listen to her help love
听她帮助爱
never ever takes you
从未将你
i will do
我将做
well in the twilight swear the matter wings
好在暮色中发誓，这事儿的翅膀
she got you jumping off the deck shoveling the overdrive
她让你从甲板上跳下来，铲掉了超速器
hey
嘿
what's this loss
这是什么损失
yes
是
they haven't been feel up to break you
他们还没有被感觉到要破坏你
do you stand us book our mind
你能忍受我们的思想吗？
see zagnvia hadn't asked to see if her feared
看到Zagnvia没有问到她是否害怕的问题
that's his lord fatak martine martine extends by monad and run
那是他的领主法塔克-马丁-马丁通过单体和运行扩展的。
destests if your hotel is mahanoine yeah
如果你的酒店是Mahanoine，那么你的命运是什么？
that's just lying anisganook
这只是在撒谎，阿尼斯加诺克
zacht vere et marilla kane
their drone ranger
他们的无人机护林员
evelonza bijifas and ron pokram
Evelonza Bijifas和Ron Pokram
they come to him the intest tsurstatan and
他们来找他的目的是为了让他知道。
dan mateonstein latindid
丹-马特恩斯坦-拉蒂德
chianoka stanister
卡诺卡-斯坦尼斯特
divine martin
神奇的马丁
gimbe in martin
马丁的Gimbe
as a dinghta that's fataxtilis martin
作为一个Dinghta，这是fataxtilis martin。
nitin combines nitin kamatsvi martin
NITIN组合NITIN KAMATSVI MARTIN
there's rash the moods have broke up to heaven
心情不好的人就会上天。
the obligaford manage meth
义务教育的管理方法
so a crookish man
原来是个骗子
control here starkstar use their paths
在这里控制starkstar使用他们的路径
darkstar control have loud and die plish by dear louder
暗星控制有响亮的和死的plish由亲爱的更响亮的
die plish for fuel control ambushlas varifer stard apu
用于燃料控制的模塑装置 Ambushlas varifer stard apu
lincoln sleepwalk stop
林肯的梦游停顿
class actions online
网上集体诉讼
using cuts
使用切割
and
和
bikes
自行车
maverick kane is done to a photograph on
特立独行的凯恩在一张照片上做了手脚。
become the operation as manstron
成为manstron的操作
the virus faste blue twin to the stoich test
病毒的味道是蓝色的，是斯托克试验的孪生兄弟。
these virus fast are an android blue twenty snish tour
这些病毒快是一个安卓的蓝色20snish之旅
dark stars are propilied
黑暗中的星辰被预言了
an aller
一个人
cloud checking for takeoff
云层检查起飞
deep record deep record go temper her to ungo type stuff go
深度记录 深度记录 脾气大的她不走样的东西去了
electric go ouda angstaya own go darkstar yakotroj
电动车欧达-安格斯塔亚自己的车暗星雅克特罗伊
dantelothashertaj
and then sweetheart
而后亲爱的
i need stefuk
我需要Stefuk
don't stop that you're staying up sex nuno on tahuba
不要停止，你是熬夜的性奴在塔乌巴
which lighting z of matlaka muffin
马特拉卡松饼的照明Z
hi is x no noy on tahuba there's going to go from afg
嗨，是X没有在Tahuba上，有要去从Afg
admiral
上将
god are the rest of this sir
诸位先生，其余的都在这里了。
he's been so full once ya'll comes he made us acclan
你们一来，他就吃得很饱，让我们吃得很饱。
math that we're all cain but the field does re operation
我们都是凯恩的数学，但该领域确实是重新运作的。
no i see that i've burned mama nearby
不，我看到我已经烧毁了附近的妈妈
and no text we have no koblima metamphunk sir
没有文字，我们没有科布利马-梅塔姆彭克先生。
nikanda yet kilmong gunawagazak yat velbon
尊敬的女士们、先生们、女士们： 你们好！我是来自中国北京的李先生，我是来自中国上海的李先生。
had many named cafe angliboten
有许多名为Angliboten的咖啡馆
okay
好的
yes uga maxim near the yacht flute data
是的uga格言附近的游艇笛子数据
temple to a stake to the partnership beer vinces fataguta
寺院对合伙企业啤酒Vinces Fataguta的股份
makaka maak
ǞǞǞ
maka manoin
玛卡-马诺因
maknoyn easter schnetz demente after their earth
纪念日后，Maknoyn和Schnetz在他们的地球上。
that's no night
那不是夜晚
no slow
不慢
math no and i
数学不和我
none fear
无所畏惧
near the home
在家附近
font chiba hits of anon
字体千叶点击率的安然
boba flashing temperature stacked
荞麦面闪光温度叠加
come sweet and run this
来吧，让我们一起努力吧
and clinist miss you
和临床医生想念你
to snake to snake
蛇对蛇
now for last two year kleiner
现在是过去两年的Kleiner
that's my sister lesson
这是我妹妹的课
maverick
特立独行
duck
鸭子
four minute
四分钟
maverick
特立独行
so i do about raisijan in a navy
我对海军中的Raisijan的看法是这样的
garfisht's medallion palobigong in
加菲斯特的奖章Palobigong在
the iron cigadianu
铁打的营盘流水的兵
netsunfilsijandrai find teach a machine up gushasanad
网友 "unfilsijandrai "找到了 "教机了 "的古沙沙。
mitt osteijnon
米特-奥斯特伊农
mit osteijnon
缓解了对 "大 "和 "小 "的依赖。
mit osteignon
缓解了压力
thoughts him kind of a third or home in an horstand vonsenishd
想到他是一个第三人或家在一个角落里的冯森尼希德。
on top fordsistofan league in viaganziges tushtam
在viaganziges tushtam的fordsistofan联盟中名列前茅
sees otton mitlavada langst tswashtana at marazine
在马拉兹看到奥顿-米特拉瓦达-朗斯特-茨瓦什塔纳。
penny tsanatoa
潘妮-萨纳托亚
thou sees enter manohir
你看到进入马诺希尔
captain
机长
ovan league does
欧文联盟确实
anastakosena hits the slim
阿纳斯塔科塞纳打出苗条
sir that's what kind vits
先生，这就是我们要做的。
he harbours yet fasca fact
他还隐藏着一个事实，那就是
my blood sister sir naya
我的血亲姐姐纳亚先生
the navy zitas nishto
海军的zitas nishto
yet nishtmere
然而nishtmere
there's a fluke target is it heston captain
有一个侥幸的目标，就是赫斯顿队长
golden foyolo shapito kana pilottena
金色的foyolo shapito kana pilottena
pilottendish laughing essen on pessen mersen
皮洛特-丹尼尔笑着说："佩森-梅森"。
pilot nibafila miss arton
飞行员Nibafila Miss Arton
so you have no adverse title to annoy the hoskiflong
所以你没有不利的称号来烦扰霍斯基弗龙
the two conftat begone
两人相见恨晚
once he come nishta and four
一旦他来到尼什塔和四
escotti and zid is the man from stratspont
Escotti和Zid是来自Stratspont的人。
ring z in enzanco tier lartin zebezazanazahangapaktat
环Z在恩桑科层拉廷Zebezazanazahangapaktat
in irnashtun nazolioft in vagna north islandsan
在伊尔纳什图的Nazolioft在瓦格纳的北岛an
north island sir
北岛先生
the animals have come to win passes and side punked
动物们都来赢取通行证，并在一旁捣乱
graduates are here forms the entgradish host in fakirtswood
毕业生在这里形成了fakirtswood的entgradish主机
scene
现场
s s algon mishmaslos
S S Algon Mishmaslos
alas gondi nora nashti gondia shots and elgan
the old ad manzi touric to top gun
老牌广告商Manzi Touric成为头号枪手
so the convectorate captain
所以对流的队长
does indicate unoswice this maverick
这也说明了这个特立独行的人是不可能的。
even anton
连安东
alexander
亚历山大
captain pete maverick mitchell
皮特-马弗里克-米切尔上尉
your hoof is the argument i can't
你的蹄子是我不能的论据
ducky sir
鸭子先生
that's what i can't compliment
这就是我无法恭维的地方
you've been admiral beau simpson
你已经是海军上将Beau Simpson了
you're commander you glob admiral beats kenzi
你是指挥官，你是地球上的上将，打败了Kenzi。
warlock yes sir
术士 是的，先生
it must sueg him your hand i don't have the shiver hushed
你的手一定很疼，我没有颤抖的感觉。
manetta's fulfill maverick
马内塔的履行特立独行
see by the adminters command zone cyclone
看到的是由钦差大臣指挥的区域旋风
the actor and artsy yagans
演员和艺术的雅戈尔
pestons and a classic ganaganon survives smite pester
捣蛋鬼和一个经典的加那加农幸存下来的捣蛋鬼
nor amitani to philahardon
也没有阿米塔尼到菲拉顿
the steel
钢材
is an illegal
是一种非法的
uran and rajongs unlagadevan
乌兰和拉琼斯-乌拉加德万
bogging and multilateralis not to upcom frustrust
阻碍和多边主义是不值得信赖的。
the stod podisia to uran is the nigafar films of abandon
对乌兰来说，Stod podisia就是放弃的Nigafar电影。
and des aragon
和德-阿拉贡
the spent are
花费的是
gonverdasia and einzats teams as armstrong
Gonverdasia和Einzats团队作为阿姆斯特朗
as the unlagats are stirt
闲人免进
before the fall betrix vagist
堕落前的贝特里克斯-瓦格斯特
the defendancy hinanim unto edition bonka in mitten deses tarts
被告人希纳尼姆的未出版版bonka in mitten deses tarts
the starl is to a gps strair zenda on tttalija borden lufthar
这颗星是在Tttalija Borden Lufthar上的一个Gps strair zenda。
katan sobidojiniga cumfjet stefan
卡坦-索比多-吉尼加-暨夫杰-斯特凡
nganavatsiongazihat
thief and alastakla hinsada
小偷和Alastakla Hinsada
and reserva luftfatsoygnotar stretsvian
和reserva luftfatsoygnotar stretsvian
the odazuga and para de effiltsin
奥达祖加和帕尔菲利辛公司
vioshamitas antegan aren't eliquen for certain
vioshamitas antegan不是Eliquen，这是肯定的。
v istiha and shets on captain
there's the egg fructor house has vines in his style
有一个鸡蛋Fructor房子有他的风格的藤蔓
and mansiti gansel luftha persi
和Mansiti Gansel Luftha Persi
romandasu barript
Romandasu Barript
is the victor house and antigua luftcumf aris unferrong
胜利之家 "和 "安提瓜岛 "都是不合法的。
via dz patricia fowl midpling
通过DZ Patricia Fowl Midpling
mr alan and amazon sir
阿兰先生和亚马逊先生
no
不
men believe in venezuela
男人相信委内瑞拉
mr smirkley you're a knift dynasty and lugabatoops brett
斯莫克雷先生，你是一个Knift王朝和Lugabatoops Brett的。
in drive often
常常在驾驶中
philist ear
幽冥之耳
there's nobody here that's if the avatting of longmen
这里没有人，如果龙门的头像是这样的
on this fast sniffing me to anandai antartonburno
在这个快速嗅觉的我到阿南戴-安塔尔顿-伯诺
ama defa finish analysom eclobazi misfortuneons captain
阿马德瓦完成分析埃克罗巴兹的不幸队长
sir bivonne desi fleeton
比沃恩-德西-弗兰登先生
bivonne de ceontareton
Bivonne de Ceontareton
ontarishan sir
ontarishan先生
viandsworth topganaps are ventanfoniangashvara and sarakpa arat
Viandsworth topganaps是Ventanfoniangashvara和Sarakpa arat。
peveranda city copa of zach's riddledsian
扎克瑞德的佩弗兰达市副本
on tv and the mission fleet
在电视上和使命舰队
keep tempo blame captain
保持节奏责备队长
this residency talk
这次驻会谈话
sir
先生
yeah bradley bradshaw
是的，布拉德利-布拉德肖
orphana marusta survived the vicensimentana martin hangarflug
奥法娜-马鲁斯塔在沧海桑田中幸存下来，马汀-亨格卢格
three vizainhofnamena
3.三轮驱动的纳姆纳(Vizainhofnamena)
good sir
好先生
targasha forfei
塔格沙-福尔菲
captain mitchell bordefong
Mitchell Bordefong队长
yeta short figureshpok and gatort from guzva and odfile
惟其如此，才会有短小的身影，才会有来自Guzva和odfile的Gatort。
saints escanazo captain
圣徒埃斯卡纳索队长
once it goes on as also
一旦它继续作为也
by iron respect sir
铁的尊重先生
espncai lera zivanshamatopganos perda
for fras thaisishanfu gardamatswei monitor
为fras thaisishanfu gardamatswei显示器
does this nishmanplat e ferguns often so insane
这个Nishmanplat e ferguns经常这么疯狂吗？
zivan nist mana yestervi zishtant nismalaf de lista
尊敬的女士们、先生们、女士们： 你们好，我是你们的朋友，我是你们的朋友，我是你们的朋友，我是你们的朋友。
zizantia offez ukunfan admiral kazanski
non icemanist einsu felish
非冰雪运动者，但也有一些人认为，这是不可能的。
and mandeni to thiefst pervondel who dearest volder
和Mandeni到小偷Pervondel谁最亲爱的Volder
anzitasida navine of us to beat nhab
我们要击败Nhab的Anzitasida Navine
past the signs of advice isn't it
过了咨询期不是吗？
see mercentes and chop nister name abademita's classed
请看Mercentes和Chop nister的名字Abademita's classed。
does he have it the electstar eins at zion captain
他是否有在锡安的Electstar Eins队长？
is he fleeting for top gun or does he flee in navidafordi navy
他是为顶级枪手而转身，还是在纳维达福尔迪海军中逃亡？
and swan to get us on his giant and undershuster
和天鹅，让我们在他的巨人和矮子上。
oh that's off the furnish fire sign
哦，这是在家具上的火牌
pete penny
彼得-彭尼
that's what stood in you yeah
这就是你的优势所在。
that's ever contested fun
有争议的乐趣
i don't know your sister desperate spy please john
我不认识你的妹妹，我想做间谍。
banaster dees margaret
Banaster dees Margaret
we don't hit marill baya cla
我们不打marill baya cla
this is a lot of me oh pete he can't do any longer booze as i
这是一个很多的我哦佩特他不能做任何更多的酒，因为我
does this did us probably
这对我们来说可能是个好消息
ishmasan
north island is the leads to ottaly mishavada tattadish susanne
北岛是通往意大利的通道，是Mishavada tattadish susanne。
hm did langa be sushan here de la nabhi fodrayanga
kaft foddrayan hmm yeah
喀夫特-福德拉扬 嗯，是的
courts not himself is being agamitam
不是自己的法院是被agamitam的
under an admiral and evistakashiktatan
隶属海军司令部，并在其领导下的evistakashiktatan
do i stay on trying to eat a manga aga
我是否要继续尝试吃漫画AGA？
privately visitor needs like a come
私人访客需要像来
naya
look quick just from him nan you think
快看就从他身上，南你觉得
you think it does this assist ah compete
你觉得它做这个辅助啊竞争
does extras or language china
是否有额外的内容或语言中国
as to akazakhazi
至于akazakhazi
disnavanzlash plitsu and a f arts english naptab
he was none of the city of nafbaznian monsters untending iraq
他不属于纳夫巴兹尼亚市的怪物，不属于伊拉克。
by the model the blanksichian srirish carton
模特儿--布莱克希安-斯里希-卡顿
ice mangrived some hurrah
冰雪聪明的人
onto miss vida and eloft and he doesn't need to forget pete
错过了维达和埃洛夫特，他不需要忘记佩特。
gloat me so on lushani she's yet stockling
欢呼雀跃，她还在为自己的 "股票 "欢呼雀跃。
elton turns it's to vida mitna raquita
埃尔顿把它交给维达-米特纳-拉基塔
i'm hinton and ernda and camphchet
我是Hinton、Ernda和Caphchet
pennyham such bad
潘尼汉姆这样的坏
as
作为
towards me fragman if i are maha
对我来说，如果我是马哈，我就会变成一个碎片。
yet see me nita
偶尔也会见到我，尼塔
exhabit nita angazin ish verse
ㄒ唬┥米芾砉ぷ鞯淖饔?
as they not in my garage madonne speed
因为他们不在我的车库里，马东娜的速度
lessons garnister sanfa
教训 加尼斯特-桑法
okay
好的
to see scooters
看到滑板车
i'm just a past
我只是一个过去
and a lady ordered in navy
和一位穿着海军制服的女士
respectless to hundred orders and henry of mantrays and eggs
不畏艰险，百折不挠，不畏艰险，不畏艰险，不畏艰险，不畏艰险。
there's my snow kai honda
这是我的雪凯本田
charlie
查理
took my light vegans and craving to our splitches is not flutes
把我的轻度素食主义者和渴望我们的分裂的人不是笛子吗？
oh come shut
哦，闭嘴
now in hat miranda
现在在帽子里的米兰达
fantastic phoenix s
梦幻般的凤凰城
what is after near the investments on this coyote
在这只土狼的投资附近有什么？
whatever happened to you so trimming here in anger datan
发生了什么事，你这么修剪在这里的愤怒DATAN
loiter does he a spagman hangman be your hammer
徘徊不前的他是个刽子手，是你的锤子。
four oshtata angsiga activa
四个oshtata angsiga activa
navy pilot with animal state eating loadcamp
海军飞行员与动物状态下的吃货训练营
upshores stop aladdins
上岸后停止阿拉丁。
zasteandarin and museumstok austin korea creek humans
Zasteandarin and museumstok austin korea creek humans
kaiku creek and uh creek like you see a honda national steason
kaiku小溪和uh小溪，就像你看到的本田全国蒸馏器一样。
he hasn't done his honda hey bet sandboy
他还没有做完他的本田，嘿嘿，打赌沙男孩
hey coyote hey
嘿，小狼嘿
verse here yes we are
诗句在这里，是的，我们在这里
it's like van best student here
这就像一个最好的学生在这里
oh he's riding unsubsided by
哦，他骑的是无侧翼的
the madison stairs blood lord bertlish
麦迪逊楼梯的血主贝特利什
nine it's been buffon's esteem off it's here
9它一直是Buffon的自尊心，它在这里
born is in for homore
诞生的是Homore
vivosto benante
寿星贝南特
both
两个
nine and hoofnam
九和蹄南
uh
呃
bob
鲍勃
bob floyd
鲍勃-弗洛伊德
dubas manoi avezo asleemore
is it yours yeah
这是你的吗？
no no bipop
不不不
bell of
的钟声
okay
好的
any mansion yeah
任何豪宅 是的
not my fear often all time on
不是我的恐惧，往往是所有的时间上
ratchet
棘轮
let's do this
让我们这样做
so if i asked us to em land the best
因此，如果我要求我们把最好的东西送到他们那里去
yeah they stuffed it about us this
是的，他们把我们的事情塞给了这个
shanditzazen shanditzelzen
陕西省人民政府办公厅 陕西省人民政府办公厅
so bittersea lessons the inductor for pops
因此，苦涩的教训是电感的弹出。
he's tidy but before the arms are ridiculous gate
他很整洁，但在手臂上有一个可笑的门。
that's all
仅此而已
my history hangman
我的历史刽子手
resist good ask
抵制好的要求
uh in your good rooster
呃，在你的好公鸡
beacon jacob tatsus is we need to hold on vats was i
烽火台雅各布-塔特苏斯是我们需要坚持的瓦特是我的。
azo
偶数
pour one gatesmarkism
浇筑一个门槛
spitzer and commando vice nasana ms yonas ms yon
斯皮策和突击队的副手纳萨纳-约纳斯-约恩女士
that's your business
那是你的事
they can't assure you
他们不能向你保证
ever the team leader
曾经的团队领导
but definitely had a structure to metropol
但肯定有一个大都市的结构
i gave him the deer forget unvigalis they assured us
我给他的鹿忘记了unvigalis，他们向我们保证。
i was a bristol immen rosta
我曾是布里斯托尔-伊门-罗斯塔的一员
those shockets diluteless thirty eight
那些令人震惊的无稀释的三十八
on bottles of canal an elastic in moment
在运河的瓶子上有一个弹性的时刻
and he must count
而他必须计算
a sleep of this town
一觉醒来
tila technically ended
蒂拉在技术上已经结束
nope underneath
不在下面
zet man
泽人
of mafenons
的马费农
descent harvard yale
血统 哈佛 耶鲁
omah chryson as a switz must venomous joanistas
Omah Chryson作为一个Switchz必须要有毒舌的Joanistas
thus is nitty flagger de veon stone's odens
这就是Nitty Flagger de veon Stone的作品。
yeta he attempts to invest in their own head
然而，他试图在自己的头上投资
convenes are in the universe then
召集人是在宇宙中，那么
you can't
你不能
do it
做到这一点
the
的
best
最好的
er it come on for bioplanet escape
来吧，为生物星球的逃亡而战。
touch me light
触摸我的光
vegans and vegan pete
素食者和素食者皮特
一万两次一万步
一万步一万步
一万步一
万步一万步
thank you for speaking
谢谢你的发言
you know love don't change a dream
你知道爱情不会改变梦想
you brought my will
你带来了我的意志
you a one and three goodness praise you take all the fire
你是一个三好的人，赞美你把所有的火。
all the
所有的
twenty but you get along and you move me i've been
二十岁，但你们相处得很好，你们让我感动，我已经
i'll take my mind
我把我的想法
your love is fine good this gracious rape all the fire
你的爱是好的，这个亲切的强奸所有的火。
she will tell
她会告诉
you go
你去
cause holy
缘于圣人
it's just a
这只是一个
fall
坠落
a stronger deck
一个更强大的甲板
good mog
好的Mog
belcombe ceon schpitzyat training names it platti
Belcombe ceon schpitzyat培训命名为platti
if in admiral bates commandantes are english strong
如果在海军上将贝茨的指挥官是英国人的强者
the al is in top gun up serventon
军队正处于最高级别的战斗状态。
the elita
菁英会
de best deveston
最佳的Deveston
the fenta comfortaganavatsiondas finders
Fenta的舒适性，AvatsionDas发现者
had glycif aheadness agashavan
曾有过甘愿为之奋斗的人。
they skip noveniga the cantada thais
他们跳过Noveniga的Cantada泰国人
about integral laugushan foshpongiptus nishmir they are a folk
关于整体的Laugushan foshpongiptus nishmir 他们是一个民间的
it's mereden year apangi fonde man ordered afro in cockpit
这是在Mereden年，Apangi Fonde的人在驾驶舱内订购了非洲人。
nor the health the phonine and verticolophitsian
也没有健康的音容笑貌。
irona phonine vertimisjon amphiu
铁道部门："我们的目标是使我们的产品和服务达到世界一流水平。
the under a health ability to reserve
下的健康能力储备
the house builders
建房者
and top gun absolute met paktisha found an island
顶尖的枪手绝对遇到了帕克提萨，发现了一个岛屿
by raishandemisjondi phonine nga master beardenzone
作者：raishandemisjondi phonine nga master beardenzone
sonifordinster said glegandea
sonifordinster说，glegandea
on their guilt as
在他们的罪状上，作为
under their best and pilot indigenous program
根据他们的最佳和试点土著计划
ye have folk acquired hat thus a inn and bibleing built
你们在民间获得了帽子，从而建立了一个旅馆和圣经。
cantazea vold in onto sheet osmartans vision leaden onto tot
captain pete mitchell
彼得-米切尔上尉
ofnama maverick
的特立独行的人
good modern
良好的现代
does f artenhampu
岂不就是F-Artenhampu
and hey
和嘿
alice pass man anywhere you flutes a bike apartheish name
爱丽斯-帕克斯的男人，你在任何地方都有一个自行车的笛子。
angi kandaspu in north ausfendish fair damage
安吉-坎达斯普在北奥芬迪什博览会上的损失
you find a bow
你找到一张弓
with a skate with a loss
亏损的溜冰鞋
above a simphonist mechandists and evil limits
在Simphonist mechandists和邪恶的限制之上
is very zephyn
是非常的zephyn
the test
测试
the avatar
头像
how to begin via
如何开始通过
medivacino globens of essagnzi mevacitova
埃塞格尼兹-梅瓦西托娃的梅迪瓦西诺球体
ready
准备好了
lieutenant branch
中尉部
yes sir
是的，先生
yes it's so unfair
是的，这太不公平了
this delicious kitten
这只美味的小猫
that's lee clandia liftandia
那是Lee Clandia Liftandia
davis vector
戴维斯矢量
good morning figure
早晨的数字
yes please take it be a consum god cause i've come from an over
是的，请把它作为一个消费神，因为我来自于一个过度。
the aniko mistanian behind in loftcam
阿尼科-米斯塔尼在LOFTCAM的背后
mourbata kind of a kid
慕容巴塔那种孩子
you describe nishti members flukewear from fifth thousand fourth
你描述尼西蒂成员的侥幸心理，从第五千四分之一开始。
the abba dance team of messimijamshis in the dhans dance vassa
乱世佳人的阿巴舞蹈队在丹尼斯舞蹈《瓦萨》中的表演
zanstri saforwick
benihanfani namshi said i'm z by the followan
benihanfani namshi说，我是z由followan的。
they're curb ochma and denton red defanons sir
他们是路边的奥克玛和丹顿的红色防卫者，先生
i'm not a pretty zoco santa
我不是一个漂亮的Zoco Santa
what's wrong zifu
怎么了，子夫
there's a staff go sharston
有一个工作人员去Sharston
but matt swan that push ups blow it turn yeah
但马特-斯旺的俯卧撑让它转身了 是的
let's go to tila pushaps as high stand istams on straining sir
让我们去蒂拉-普萨普斯，作为高站位的伊斯坦斯，在紧张的先生。
ya men dear gentlemen eat better goods scam to the boat
亲爱的先生们，吃点好东西吧。
van voice history of them other forms as deaths
梵音历史的他们其他形式的死亡
emma sent out time
艾玛送出的时间
we don't get fooled again
我们不会再受骗了
so delivering
所以要交付
physically thug i'm here to target if i have to feel
身体上的暴徒，我在这里的目标，如果我不得不觉得
dali dali dali maria cup that leaks back then where you leads me
大理 大理 大理 玛丽亚 杯子当时就漏了，你把我带到哪里去了？
hey meg what's your wingman
嘿，MEG，你的僚机是什么？
who's there for this stool
谁在那里为这个凳子
it's been hit a year it's coming pattern pattern badgets
它已经被打了一年，它的到来模式模式坏了。
hey back extract pleasure we can attack
嘿，回来吧，我们可以攻击
you were such a guard in a scream gun at a thriller
你就是这样一个在惊悚片中用枪尖叫的卫兵
a man has constant in us
人在江湖身不由己
despite message
尽管留言
rooster the best to keep your hopes mess out them in the stairs
公鸡是最好的，以保持你的希望，他们在楼梯上的混乱。
here in my nose
在我的鼻子里
here in my nose shit
在我的鼻子里拉屎
that's a
那是一个
physic plunger get food
物理柱塞获取食物
smith's not english via zan
史密斯不是英国人，通过ZAN
zatia banish and yetzlist embassian mayo garusta
Zatia Banish and yetzlist embassian mayo garusta
oh hey look
哦，嘿，看
at this
在此
i'm sorry sir
我很抱歉，先生
monster baby on both
两者的怪物宝宝
i
can't
不可能
do it
做到这一点
move it on him that's an unbean hangman that's that henk workon
在他身上动一动，那是一个没有豆子的刽子手，那是他的工作。
yet wingman abstitulous detective gaspinoid
然而翼人节制的侦探气质
an additional phoenix listen in oscar fire
在奥斯卡火中再听一次凤凰的声音
so long an additionist munland
再见了，加法主义的Munland
easy to ask for boss moving her contest it's another one
易要求老板搬走她的比赛，这是另一个问题。
shoving you from her tang man
把你从她身边推开的唐人
you are shouted to harsher to the arizmanand flossier
你对阿里兹曼和弗洛西尔喊得更严厉了。
record amen it's time to lyrics young this is a tourist philips
唱片阿门，是时候歌词年轻，这是一个旅游菲利普斯
okay
好的
phoenix i can't in the same
凤凰网我不能在同一个
phoenix
凤凰
it's been taught ashley there's innocent yenzo it's back man
它已经被教导阿什利有无辜的Yenzo它回来的人
hold this there hold this there
拿着这个，拿着这个
answers
答案
anna defense under archie under
阿奇下的安纳防御
yes
是
an ace
王牌
i like my rooster and i need a pesony of haggar stone
我喜欢我的公鸡，我需要一个哈格尔石的小石头
that's what's underneath nine zaga
这就是九寨沟下面的东西
why says that's thracendian maverick and shanti's nevasto mahon
为什么说那是Thracendian Maverick和Shanti的Nevasto Mahon？
here disney's son put some tougher stick there
迪斯尼的儿子在这里放了一些更硬的棍子
but he guns at sight here
但他在这里看到了枪
see timmy's chest
见Timmy的胸部
the cumbling descentoads can lost in
喃喃自语的后裔会迷失在
i stumbled in
我跌跌撞撞地走了进来
either don't search your line the boss for constantly announce
要么不搜你的线，老板不断宣布
don't cut the general tied off tank
不要剪断一般的捆绑式水箱
the chief of thazzon skin russa he can so cheap sink bbz
泰森皮肤的首领Russa他可以如此廉价地沉没在BBZ中
把他摔倒踩死
the gun right is the gun right fuel spider yeah
枪的权利是枪的权利，燃料蜘蛛是的。
it is not my time
时不我待
泰迪杀车
竟然喊咗中 step city 门已经 sighter
竟然喊了中步城门已经视线的人
puffy puffy
蓬松的蓬松的
dinosaurs listen to santra
恐龙听桑塔纳的话
go rouge the duhastin he hold down cheese
去胭脂红的杜哈斯丁，他按住了奶酪
yes to teeth
是的，对牙齿
just wait to have the sanishos
等着吃香肠吧
i'm just
我只是
individual
个人
to dumped two perfect roaster
甩掉两个完美的烤炉
made this behind of english
这是在英语后面做的。
not good that's iced
不好，这是冰的
rooster that's iced man
公鸡那是冰冷的男人
mendes to your enthusiasm the theatre bigo beats to house fling
门德斯对你的热情 剧院的BIGO节拍对房子的欢愉
kinda zaga
有点像Zaga
hutsu
胡蝶
it really is a mission
这真的是一项任务
above vendidish hoshmeis and fleeting via amendemit hangman
以上是vendidish hoshmeis和转瞬即逝，通过amendemit hangman。
freedom mcmille what sometimes elder does manipapira in bahatan
自由麦克米勒 有时长者会在巴哈坦的操纵下做什么？
what
什么
dear them maverick
亲爱的他们特立独行
have that much for hinatosihani akadimigi
有这么多的hinatosihani akadimigi
atmospheria the good costs
大气层的良好成本
sean garnish spontanvia and testanics oh
this is kobra manogafonin and as the aladi umbrankan
这是科布拉-马诺加福宁，作为阿拉迪-乌姆布兰肯的一员。
so i in chicago navidas in
所以我在芝加哥的纳维达斯在
won't visit us tier tester and the house has come
不会访问我们的层级测试员和房子已经来了
i'm busy the house come sir
我很忙，家里的事，来吧，先生
you're the miss you are not the erasing
你就是那个错过的人，你不是那个被抹去的人
these are pilot not empty on this isn't it sir
这些都是试点，不是空的，不是吗，先生？
apoyta informian zion ciadan martin
基金会的信息：锡安-西亚丹-马丁
uba euron training explan shriftly
乌巴乌龙培训的解释是：shriftly
ontos that nickets get in that automaena australia
在澳大利亚的自动售货机上，有一个小男孩在玩耍。
ganemic martini de mindas tour sir
de mindus tour songanist captain
德-明德巡回演唱会队长
sir
先生
what's this does
这是做什么的
and figure to her
以及对她的身材
let's see on their minutes to a surface if look we're gonna
让我们看看在他们的分钟到一个表面，如果看我们要去
so you can't not answer any of a timing lounge captain
所以你不可能不回答任何一个计时休息室的队长
here cayori
这里是cayori
see denison
见丹尼森
the sister nile again the deserman na na na nave mean
又是尼罗河姐妹，又是德玛西亚人，又是尼罗河的意思。
come to dennis pekanfor
来找丹尼斯-佩坎弗
the inhabitanta
栖息地ta
bradshaw
布雷德肖
so vicious dear
如此恶毒的亲爱的
hey see you mr walskamore hey math
嘿，看到你，Walskamore先生，嘿，数学。
amelia yes bias it's been kozkavan yeah
Amelia 是的，偏向于它一直是Kozkavan 是的。
the bama confense of
共和国总统府
nine it's coming off a bioman assurance
9它是来自于一个生物人的保证
hey if you could send him dead lip manzanafro of hawaii mom
嘿，如果你能给他送去夏威夷妈妈的死唇曼萨纳夫罗
mafsaka shooted the gate
马夫萨卡拍下了大门
oh mafti kang kofta singh push it off
哦，Mafti Kang Kofta Singh 推掉它
vermit is undecliba glitchen
沉默寡言的人是不道德的。
captain emana
Emana船长
and hawkti coherta captain
和Hawkti coherta队长
marshlos that's bought mos and evaft
购买了Mos和Evaft的Marshlos
econish plus mine cedriconsnish
it must fantastic mongland hamsions hotes gazacht
它必须是神奇的Mongland hamsions hotes gazacht
about econic aligns egren
关于Econic aligns egren
danimhatimotoa
邓丽君
well i'm bring their starvaft 这么着还不敢出啊
我把他们的Starvaft 这么着还不敢出啊
it can have
它可以有
hey there's noah i think i'm out of town
嘿，这是诺亚，我想我出城了。
my city says
我的城市说
this is after schnappoint the same book on the vegan
这是在Schnappoint之后，关于素食者的同一本书。
to vista honda navy
到维斯塔-本田海军
exactly kind of water penny it's under their loss
确切地说，是在他们的损失下的水笔。
but it's that germany jump from koopson icon put it on excess
但它是德国从Koopson图标上跳下来的，把它放在多余的地方。
he said that luna lion
他说，鲁纳狮
yes that's the
是的，这就是
good against the engine of colbert
对抗科尔伯特的引擎的好办法
and there's four diggings of twin
有四次挖出的双胞胎
colbert sixteen that's it yep
科尔伯特十六岁，这就是它。
you know
你知道
zones yet
区域尚未
mr behind
后面的先生
or here
或在这里
they now fly now
他们现在飞起来了
let's consider the name
让我们考虑一下这个名字
lunk is an enemy if i'd
伦克是一个敌人，如果我
it's been a situation here for va
这里的情况已经持续了很长时间。
see minnesotan
见明尼苏达人
deaden
死气沉沉
nazo
纳佐
go to napped
去打瞌睡
not penny
一分钱都没有
sight is the oyster fat
看到的是牡蛎的脂肪
fanza answer missoulus
Fanza回答Missoulus
and borden are unproven that i'm sharma's fear fruit
和Borden是未经证实的，我是Sharma的恐惧果。
turing in smirhoden
在Smirhoden的图灵
see fleeing their teasing smile in canyon some tear
在峡谷中看到逃离他们挑逗的笑容，有些泪水
deba rasta river asto charagon ink the borden of tarkatan gaziat
德巴拉斯特河阿斯托-查拉贡墨水塔卡坦-加西亚特的波尔登
these assams sent turtley
这些阿萨姆人送来了Turtley
abbas isn't concepted on the inhibits of a tiding
阿巴斯并不打算在泰德的抑制上做文章
mist in kenyan de hunter well
雾在肯尼亚德亨特井
they find investors kindas of crankis or teeth on
他们发现投资者的曲棍球或牙齿在
their indoists of ling
他们的凌云阁
welconada ferrari ciaosburn
威克纳达-费拉里-西亚斯本
antism tark is the rfluca ignonatfus maximo
反对派是 "反对派 "的代表。
then zitizuhu ibashitan afasidashara
然后zitizuhu ibashitan afasidashara
on season taught
季节性教学
either flukish finished catatric textona testic norton minimum
侥幸地完成了 "卡特里克 "文本，测试了 "诺顿 "的最低限度。
cypistamteer that's minehard mie norton
cypistamteer 这是我的硬伤 Mie Norton
by campstead stephen ganatzonov and ananbaza sparachden
作者：坎特德-斯蒂芬-加纳佐诺夫和阿南巴扎-斯帕拉赫登
and luftkampking the neon f arte
和Luftkampking the neon f arte
and susan taught
和苏珊教
the sardines in iran
伊朗的沙丁鱼
does cidoshayton on vexian before these are jets arkano de sean
在这些喷气机之前，Cidoshayton在vexian上做的事是Arkano de sean的喷气机。
salms the absafamen
荒诞不羁的人
the size detaired verbs yagari sagagnasi
规模化的动词yagari sagagnasi
is he fleeing and hotel
他是否在逃亡，是否在酒店
navigatsuan sustained in canyons immuliet
在峡谷中持续航行的Navigatsuan immuliet
nationalizedosian canyon fleeting the sushi
国家化的峡谷，转瞬即逝的寿司
vertison to the infination arcade and how that sublime
纵横交错的商场，以及那个崇高的
you
你
anga de colvin des toshtaka vote in the gay craft of iran carla
安加-德-科尔文-德-托什塔卡在伊朗的同性恋工艺中投票卡拉
presently alone suzanne as blue does he angel and zac
目前单独的苏珊娜作为蓝色的他的天使和扎克
that's my entities autoits the merguandriac jones site
这是我的实体，我的实体是Merguandriac Jones的网站。
by the hartignubung las miss hawishangin
由Hartignubung las miss hawishangin提供。
maximala flukir dianad fus tied piston tier diamino
最大的Flukir Dianad Fus 捆绑的活塞层Diamino
secret
秘密
ten minutes some tea
十分钟后喝茶
enemy no departs
敌人没有离开
copy of hercus in these cats
这些猫中的赫库斯副本
varhamsensi taught the ahandi de la hunatfuskansa de parhan
瓦尔哈姆森西教的阿汉迪-德-胡纳特福斯坎萨-德-帕尔汉
and anna aquitad unservished night
和Anna Aquitad未被服务的夜晚
vahahamsensi taught the shape apkabamastons and nissakuvan
Vahahamsensi教授的形状apkabamastons和nissakuvan
that's famine short gabasangonte
那是饥荒的矮子加巴桑贡特
nissaukomonitsiashakansandri abandin
几内亚比绍共和国政府的代表
the familiar of tiberdigo markshiptiyat
熟悉的Tiberdigo markshiptiyat
ken sir
肯先生
valhamaticova zuballashed as you canton us surround for briefing
你在我们周围做简报的时候，Valhamaticova Zuballashed也在这里。
zanzi sneezed mia
瓒子打了个喷嚏 米娅
zanzi sana familia
hangman langzama de kanye verdanga
Hangman langzama de kanye verdanga
nigga to you playbackers winters got to earn
黑人对你的回放者温特必须要挣钱
oop is too snamer ah card of this this is fluid unsuzine
OOP是太Snamer啊，这个卡是流动的unsuzine的。
lanzama ferdant is confidential
lanzama ferdant是保密的
you can't need my titan
你不可能需要我的泰坦
rostale and saint fancy's economic sweden mir
罗斯泰尔和圣芳济的经济瑞典奇迹
be a shot from the ski swindish kite is good
从滑雪场射出的风筝是好的
the slime you got a flip from that canon near god
粘液，你从那个大炮那里得到了一个翻转的机会，近乎于神。
if you aim bird swindish can't hope brushtam is in salanza
如果你的目标是鸟，斯温迪什就不能希望布鲁斯坦在萨兰萨。
yes antamblim in the head of khanas record
是的，Antamblim在Khanas记录的头部
the swam least in don't tell me a hand daniga swindish kite
在不要告诉我一个手daniga swindish风筝的游泳最少。
it can a shuff
它可以是一个洗牌
see how can you feel no valhams and c valham is the team taught
看，你怎么能觉得没有瓦勒姆和C-瓦勒姆是球队的教头呢？
sir
先生
a sister pilot ganskino
姐妹飞行员甘斯基诺
escape niche not envict the massions of fleeing
逃亡的龛位没有设想到逃亡的massions
look up here sasanthanis
抬头看看这里，萨桑塔尼斯
by des a massion must hear their man vi maverick fleeing
在DES一个massion必须听到他们的人VI特立独行的逃亡
order their man company's metroic
订购他们公司的Metroic
it's like the kind of beladigonzine
它就像那种贝拉迪戈辛一样
and thoshafstawas thus is imionist
而这些都是模仿主义的。
israelis nikridisian du frix
以色列人Nikridisian du frix
khansavatif dazzuzalas lieutenant we have seen an encamphiana
khansavatif dazzuzalas中尉，我们已经看到了一个营地。
of adam nivoras kanpi
阿达姆-尼沃拉斯-坎皮的故事
lord ye alibtat
大王
nastana air
Nastana Air
his knitted site and de fagang hatsa denton
他编织的网站和de fagang hatsa denton
that's so desperate titan rooster
这真是令人绝望的泰坦公鸡
why do you have a time to get us memorica flown
为什么你有时间让我们的纪念品飞起来？
and the floor
和地板
hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿
he's my locker alizo hey hey hey
他是我的储物柜Alizo 嘿嘿嘿
this high set at least that's sort for these in mission
至少在任务中是这样分类的
there's high sets
有高套
the worst that's all
最坏的情况就是这样
on z vis and that's all
在z vis上，这就是全部
seduct for vectoritan
诱惑力
never rick
永恒的Rick
is this your dada
这是你的爸爸吗？
this vice norman he meant
他说的这个 "诺曼 "是指
she couldn't leave them at all
她根本就不能离开他们
so goddess playing the strats of gaval
所以，女神玩的是加瓦尔的strats。
sarah stood mr land
萨拉站在土地先生面前
agnera
琼格纳
biggest man and wingman
最大的男人和僚机
but
但
sarcas is magnific
讽刺是伟大的
god
神
whose doesn't matter how famish being deemed but he's guitar nap
他被认为有多饥渴并不重要，但他在吉他上打盹。
he started
他开始
open videos first in
打开视频首先在
the shot to go off to forgive me
打响了原谅我的枪声
do you miss your honest and vinegar slave on
你想念你的诚实和醋的奴隶吗？
do you want to snish back
你要不要回来？
brilliant alisa pasijiman beaten gun
辉煌的阿里萨-帕西吉曼被枪击
i spit falonish for me rasishiman undone
我为我的拉西曼吐出了法罗尼西，我为我的拉西曼吐出了法罗尼西。
and in torchik a bit of falonisht
和在Torchik的一点falonisht
dosishimbeville to fleeing shake me
逃亡中的我被震动了
you guys need me
你们需要我
it's been kelly horace
它一直是凯利-霍勒斯
it's become for me lord
对我来说，它已经成为主宰
and a navy fleek
和一个海军舰队
it's accomplished arthur and vassiche spin
亚瑟和瓦西奇的旋转已经完成了
some envious spin
羡慕嫉妒恨
the authoristas does
作家们的做法
simpsonic contests as nishtasvas roosterville
辛普森尼的比赛是Nishtasvas roosterville的比赛
assassinishtasvassi navy
刺杀者是海军
there's our pandemiclets to smigafiat
这就是我们的大宗商品。
the answer gon for me here then the storm
我的答案在这里，然后是风暴
then he never is a mission shake
那么他永远不会是一个任务的摇动
come devil i need you to talk
来吧，魔鬼，我需要你来谈谈
but very he needs chicken cup here
但他在这里需要鸡肉杯
for the midwest knife outside
为中西部地区的刀具外
so that's all come to interim avalian
因此，所有这些都是临时性的，阿瓦利亚
yes yes
是的是的
yes
是
the navy bloud memoric
海上丝绸之路 "纪念馆
their younger
他们的年轻
bloud memoric
纪念品
thou on marbage footage khans
你对垃圾镜头的看法是：Khans
thou on bister emen are here
你在Bister Emen上是这样的
dark eyes
黑眼睛
through others
通过他人
i'm zahana where's the best pilot
我是Zahana，哪里有最好的飞行员？
today
今天
isn't sure no moment who you need vanity
不知道你需要谁的虚荣心的时刻
take it slowly i'm stepping to your toe to toe
慢慢来吧，我正在向你的脚趾方向迈进。
i should be skin honey believes you but i am really not
我应该相信你，但我真的不相信你。
in dreams alive
在梦中活着
nineteen ninety nine year olds are you everybody right
19.99岁的人，你们都对吗？
dancing on the clouds being there i ain't worried about it
在云上跳舞，在那里我不担心。
are you worried about it
你担心吗？
i don't know what you've been told
我不知道你被告知了什么
but tommy's running out so spinning like it's gold
但汤米已经用完了，所以像金子一样旋转。
i'm living like a nazi rose got no regrets even when i'm
我活得像个纳粹玫瑰，无怨无悔，即使当我
are you worried about it
你担心吗？
i ain't worried about it
我不担心这个问题
sir what's this that's here
先生，这是什么东西？
there's a stock fight
有一场股票大战
football offensive on defensive off ein mine
橄榄球的进攻和防守，是我的工作。
big event his flower that's your
大事件，他的花是你的
length of your
你的长度
talents to tear
撕裂的人才
啊
啊啊啊
worry about it
担心它
sorry skiing
对不起，滑雪
therefore i made a solid account see today's buying a fight oh
因此，我做了一个坚实的帐户，看到今天的购买战斗哦。
good
很好
do you want to mirror your battle scientists
你是否想反映你的战斗科学家
there are few best sets of fifteen and star martin stinkers yeah
有几个最好的套装15和明星马丁臭味相投是的
you had a sticker school
你有一个贴纸学校
she bought him a fire
她给他买了一把火
hiding fit is in my nansee snacked on his behind van
躲在我的Nansee小吃他的背后的面包车是合适的
why did he doesn't have heard me
他为什么不听我的？
we should say yep i can't
我们应该说是的，我不能
does it yell for throunds like
它是否会像喊救命一样喊叫
he must see maddie maria ign and feed a mahanasa
他必须看到马蒂-玛丽亚点燃和喂养一个马哈纳萨。
kinda nice and shadow
还算不错，有阴影
but a sparrooster also
但也是一只麻雀
the hypdanats vanitas at the navy argument immediate
在海军的争论中，Hypdanats vanitas立刻就会出现。
not in yours and a loft bong across it
不在你那里，而在对面的一个阁楼上。
you saw
你看到
then what a vitanist has afflict it's not as army goes
那么，维塔纳人所受的折磨就不像军队那样了。
it must have seen first crazy before the stop arthur
它必须在停止之前看到第一个疯狂的亚瑟
advice roostered us
忠告是我们的公鸡
where's his guitar nabavatami ema nataran
他的吉他在哪里 nabavatami ema nataran
farhams are as ianatran
法拉第斯人就像Ianatran一样
do you have to say he died come out hmm
你非得说他死了才出来吗？
make a positive artisan dinner for the one night
在一个晚上做一个积极的工匠晚餐
no um
不 嗯
good if you eventually get specific act
好，如果你最终得到具体的行为
like
喜欢
divides
划分
this darkness does a shrubberiteist
这种黑暗做了一个shrubberiteist
on to stay yet survived
还没活下来
yes you
是的，你
have good doctors left by karen karen has come
卡伦-卡伦的 "好医生 "已经离开了。
it's gigaboda yeah kiss me master shobaska gason
它是Gigaboda 是的，亲吻我的主人Shobaska Gason
nine shongood
九重奏
it's marty of us
是我们的殉道者
it's congratulator
这是在祝贺你
matt
亚光
that's all
仅此而已
he was and forbidden to have nothing
他是和禁止有什么
yesterday with the blanket gun
昨天用毯子枪
there's a sniffion that is the state
有一个嗅觉，那就是国家
the vice does he mind
恶习不嫌多
okay
好的
that's right
没错
i'll be sure if we need us let's tomorrow's fence now
如果我们需要，我肯定会让我们的明天的围栏现在。
we've hadn't seen la lange might danced
我们还没有看到拉-兰格可能会跳舞
after my las ethically
以道德的方式照顾我的女儿
how'd you get up
你怎么起来的
reggae no need to do that as hats
雷鬼，不需要像帽子那样做。
good model the uran and raishaongs anga
良好的模式，乌兰和莱昂斯的昂加
yet seal vitroya betrotes the risan arts about it in st tarden
然而，在圣塔登，海豹突击队与利桑艺术的关系。
but all urans were unlagagi leford
但所有的乌兰巴托人都是乌兰巴托人。
that's producted in her missionatum i nevahur forfelict
这是在她的任务中产生的，我从来没有想过要去偷懒。
omtefah hindundas des gazamte tarldwich starlong contaminiatot
奥姆特法赫-辛杜达斯-德-冈萨雷斯-塔尔德维奇-星隆污染事件
sir esas nakanaphan
先生ESAS NAKANAPHAN
on steve looks like alfaikaska
在Steve身上看起来像Alfaikaska
florga dena louder de befilvitatsu mahan
大声点！""我的天！""我的天！""我的天！""我的天！""我的天！"。
the plazis acquired in a tuna machinenes and
在一个金枪鱼机器中获得的广场和
shadon firina furtemasur
Shadon Firina Furtemasur
on ea uba limb visi visson befinitissiandaga tushansviban
m ndanflu gains his old fought uba and in reckon schwartzfuba
恩丹弗鲁获得了他的老战友乌巴，并在考虑施瓦茨弗巴。
so kenzian gillingston miklisha who are friggan
因此，Kenzian Gillingston Miklisha谁是friggan？
on the mayansish miklishan anger of swing
关于玛雅人的米格利什人的愤怒的摆动
its seal
它的印章
is the nine shlock punk to understand my dry mate and brighter
是九大骗子朋克，了解我的干友和更多的亮点
their opposite subject makitas seal medim laser
其相反的主题makitas seal medim laser
the esther hotter to replace the amir homemad and a razor
替换阿米尔的埃斯特热尔和一把剃须刀
glength bombard and a liftosluka
轰炸机的长度和升降机的长度
taruchan strait and earth known for its writer hotter
塔鲁干海峡和地球以其作家更热而闻名
there's a tunana mines
有一个Tunana矿区
ditzwriter hotter
笨蛋作家更热
that's in finan shos
这是我的工作
on such a test
在这样的测试中
thus is tuna nomadsway
因此，金枪鱼是游牧民族的一种方式。
then isa teams to sifa feared
那么伊萨团队对西法的恐惧
the name is he miss younger shattered
他的名字是他错过了年轻的破碎
the arp fluke is an extremist
阿帕奇是个极端分子
stike flute manoeuvre on this kingdom back to pin
在这个王国里的长笛演习，回到了针脚。
and zochtela ostique by degrash windicaid
has menderston's aft gear
拥有Menderston的船尾设备
nine minimum the eva lustons granted earth
九个最小的艾娃-鲁斯通授予地球
arts and league by zeben kamafanth
Zeben Kamafanth的艺术和联盟
there's a ciofitsiela grandeur
有一个Ciofitsiela宏伟的目标
on the missountsu baliban businesses
关于Missountsu baliban企业
evashrad alfrenzia fruits actor bfb
埃瓦士拉-阿尔弗伦西亚水果演员BFB
the gig rifters and zoshtagatsuranzi fast thousand kilovian
GIG RIFTERS和ZOSHTAGATSURANZI的快速千里眼
yashira stout eura verbizard yahra lone inputia nazesi
Yashira stout eura verbizard Yahra lone inputia nazesi
nanila fantaf demost
纳米拉-范塔夫演示
surrenders from isison kemphomas and amused almeidae tsavia
伊西森-肯波马斯和逗趣的阿尔梅科-沙威亚的投降
and ganaudans in the amphavon bassin
和Ganaudans在Amphavon Bassin中。
thus
因此
it's the taurus sona
它是金牛座的索纳
then zia chef
那么齐亚厨师
and his ten in bags of the english tang zigarada
和他的十袋英式唐装Zigarada
be extending barai franti henradas
延长Barai Franti Henradas
vianzi angush vinish cadfilian
Vianzi angush vinish cadfilian
inna hope fanzi couldn't in vianzi metra kittenbashas
希望FANZI不能在Vianzi metra kittenbashas。
the alek and linger and held the gay kraft abadashi
阿莱克和徘徊，并举行了同性恋的卡夫阿巴达什
bring z on your fruct circandi belassamskansa
带来Z对你的果实circandi belassamskansa
sir
先生
estasibahabmapa the anthrot of tissafaga
伊斯塔西巴哈布玛，提萨法加的蚁人
licked a linebamp halotnam cockpit
舔了一下线路板哈洛特南的驾驶舱
visit alspapa
访问Alspapa
huh not to be east us
不做东的我们
blue teams you hold an attacked shit this memory
蓝队你持有攻击性的狗屎这个内存
that's some type of matia here
那是某种类型的马蒂亚
it's been a game now of our plancourse blue team
这已经是我们蓝队的一场比赛了
guilleria guanazi
sponsorshire lakes fanons j lower
保荐人湖泊法农斯-J-贝勒
i'm here on the demon of knotton diana insider
我在这里对诺顿-戴安娜的恶魔的内线
what's the institute
什么是研究所
cross hype isn't glassed out
跨越式的炒作并不玻璃化
i've done some
我已经做了一些
see
见
it
它
luis ian
this is uh who is memory
这是谁的记忆
there's six minor chance come stand here
有六个小的机会来站在这里
celen sister 我仆人不理 sir
Celen sister 我仆人不理 先生
自从上司奉上 swenty
自从上司奉上swenty
受气之流发送呢个字
睇你睇咩啊你睇我咁叻
tila first lover economy
蒂拉第一情人经济
coyote common
郊狼共
coyote oslanton oh god dancing she looked
小狼奥斯兰顿 哦，上帝啊，她在跳舞，她看起来
they smith up
他们的工作
they shang me shine
他们让我闪亮登场
come
来
come to coyote
到郊区来
come come here
来吧，来这里
hey odi alice okay alice okay
嘿，欧迪-艾利斯，好吧，艾利斯，好吧
alice okay get me there
爱丽斯 好的，让我去那里
good good that's high start
很好很好，这是一个很好的开始
that's not enough
这还不够
it's open up
开放了
hold it back hold it back
拖住它 拖住它
phoenix forever statsuk
凤凰传奇
the rest of the ghost a sweet dish now
其余的鬼魂现在是一个甜蜜的盘子
oh my god
哦，我的上帝
ruman rumor
谣言
don't fire live back rate and i should host a sleep back
不要解雇活的回率，我应该主持一个睡眠回率。
phoenix bob i'll stay i'll stay you know i'm not
凤凰城鲍勃 我将留下 我将留下 你知道我不会的
you can only go straight
你只能走直线
kanakantana bear yes
卡纳坎塔纳熊 是
we are not being expecting ordering an order
我们没有被期望订购一个订单
you can't just extend ostique ostique ostique
你不能只是延长Ostique Ostique Ostique Ostique
see behind the phoenix and pop so we'll go back to the bananas
看到后面的凤凰和流行，所以我们将回到香蕉上。
and let's get in good
并让我们在良好的
good susan
好苏珊
a shop not knee in wingman follow on
一家商店不跪在翼人的跟前
tars tuglik venue is longer no flexed pasietas
塔斯-图格利克场地不再是弯曲的帕西塔斯了
as for the end of the game
至于游戏的结束
who has loised rin can a fall
跌跌不休
can a kinder
能否有一个更友好的
nieman delm de toward and her upstairst
尼曼-德尔姆-德朝和她的第一份工作
you know rosa
你知道罗莎
shall i have a mission
我应该有一个任务
aram hasta for hinnatasi shafti arcademiguea
尊敬的各位来宾，大家好！我是来自中国人民大学的王晓东，我叫王晓东。
aram has such men in vegas ted
阿兰在拉斯维加斯有这样的人吗？
the vastness behind the rightful fear
正当恐惧背后的浩瀚无边
huh so it's a fling we do none
哼，所以说我们是在打情骂俏。
there's labour to fuckerson then i'm instinctive at all
有劳动的fuckerson然后我是本能的在所有的
next to dang
挨着当当
not so hundred they knew their open tank space to toad club mia
没有那么多，他们知道他们的开放式水箱空间给了蛤蟆俱乐部米亚。
my daughter tandiki rot
我的女儿坦迪基腐烂
it's marnish denzen fila
它是马尼什-邓森-菲拉。
maverick
特立独行
pull
牵引
it on fire
着火了
ekanwa anne massagarad emphanton
Ekanwa anne massagarad emphanton
names is a tad
名称是一个小的
sophia vizibrah
Sophia Vizibrah
self finally serve if you haven't got a tit
闲着也是闲着，就自个儿来吧。
you monsieur hear my name it is turning up yet
先生，您听到我的名字了吗？
sir
先生
c votend in chopped off garnished captain t missis baratso
剁碎了的C型投票器，配上队长T missis baratso。
cia zeez ottenda fizzang does he sent there's team mustan glom
ia zeez ottenda fizzang 他是否派人去了那里的团队mustan glom
sir the steezen misjongaflogan
先生，你是一个很聪明的人。
vietna gun on c m z nuagaliatas de snish merkelhist
越南的枪在C M Z nuagaliatas de snish merkelhist上。
sir zeezend ross captain
Zeezend ross先生，队长
for emma
为艾玛
sir of that's just alice
先生，这只是爱丽丝
the upscale
高档次的
stood my light
站在我的光
as we stayed soon
因为我们很快就留下来了
as i stood
当我站在
there's your vibelab mirano
这是你的Vibelab Mirano
thomas sapstein big toic fin nine penny
托马斯-萨普斯泰因的大号Toic Fin九分钱
he's been lost
他已经迷失了方向
this is for by
这是由
pete mender and wingman the olden various
皮特-曼德和僚机的旧时代
chemistry vita
化学简历
to give steet and for half
给予指导，并提供一半的
thus in tiny pilot
因此，在小小的试点中
and in earned it was passion
而在赚取的是激情
the studios knee miles for time
工作室里的膝盖是用来换取时间的
his rest is right now
他的休息就在现在
but if it does identify
但如果它确实确定了
the spicy
辣的
captain mitchell is sniffling at your house spirit
米切尔船长在你的房子里流泪的精神
on the poetic of the snoya missions parameter
关于斯诺亚任务参数的诗意
so it's until it's yet fear minuten
因此，它是直到它的恐惧分钟
see fleeing met giringa raggersfindishkat in des tarley nine
看到逃亡中遇到的Giringa Raggersfindishkat in des tarley nine
nichnel arts fiona its fancy knotten
Nichnel arts fiona its fancy knotten
sir abaham near the flute target and excitants are up to fun
阿巴哈姆先生在长笛目标附近和激进分子在一起玩耍
none lieutenant geagung fine flute targarhamse
没有中尉格贡细笛塔格拉罕斯
anna rayeloshans we stay neroshansen by coley zunmet and embac
Anna Rayeloshans We Stay Neroshansen by Coley Zunmet and Embac
the vendas silas kosarahua ungifen
西拉斯-科萨拉瓦-恩吉芬的卖点
etwa of who are the north lehigh in vant does
在VANT中，谁是北莱赫的人？
sriatsva de lasa tilafason
斯里茨瓦-德-拉萨-蒂拉法森
a barashtik flukmit extreme horn geekhaftenan fat
一个Barashtik flukmit extreme horn geekhaftenan fat
we had some type of list us
我们有一些类型的名单，我们
memory garden range control
记忆花园范围控制
emanthropop bondeifer a bit of golfer test slagger
Emanthropop bondeifer a bit of golfer test slagger
uh memory kia range control test packaged five
呃......记忆起亚范围控制测试包五
the other things kind of trading smoke from the anchor type sir
其他的事情是一种交易的烟雾从锚类型先生
martinez if you get lost in
如果你迷失在
crang on this chapter you it's my renault in fifteen sequin
在这一章中，你是我的雷诺，在十五的亮片。
it's my fifteen on merclay
这是我在Merclay上的第15次演出
stacks you can die it's all ice
你会死的，都是冰。
刚才咋害你个事啊
不要
god
神
the album michael nashmir
迈克尔-纳什米尔的专辑
gallaga gabrat captain
加拉加-加布雷特队长
iron as al tamsi bevis and dusti zimisjonga floyton verden khan
铁打的营盘流水的兵，流水的营盘，铁打的营盘，铁打的营盘，铁打的营盘，铁打的营盘，铁打的营盘，铁打的营盘，铁打的营盘。
felight of the einsegardon toubelin
埃因斯加东-图贝林号 "之光
under azades hermsean multi million dollar
在阿扎德-赫姆塞斯的领导下，价值几百万美元的
militaire flute circustoine
军人长笛Circustoine
on the sophaenovizaga flogundas is for nivida fluktogli sandart
关于sophaenovizaga flogundas是为nivida fluktogli sandart的。
iceman has snitched madame zitzibashitzen
冰人告发了Zitzibashitzen夫人
eshaba alice vassiche and militia garistan
埃斯哈巴-艾利斯-瓦西奇和民兵加里斯坦
dana uniranhafter and la songbaha
Dana Uniranhafter和La Songbaha
eisova seris too thus laden mana pilot
埃索瓦-塞里斯也是这样的拉登法力飞行员
nonville mercliftena fog demesiona riskian
order
秩序
there's killage manicover year
有杀戮的狂欢年
on mahazi tomsh van fur
关于mahazi tomsh van fur
sir iglobertifaguras admiraz varain retourgesh captain
伊格罗贝尔-费古拉斯-阿迪拉兹-瓦拉因-雷图格什先生，队长
great him it was
伟大的他是
can't make sure
难保
you're going to hear
你将会听到
my hands on starts
我的手开始
as far in the element in supreme
迄今为止，在最高的元素中
yedow and yerdaphonin said tsurin bestener bestene
yedow和yerdaphonin说tsurin bestener bestene
these are stanazeers kutsella mission
这些都是斯坦纳泽尔人的任务。
thou of petitish men and childhood of nist's unders
你是小人物，你是尼斯特的童年。
van ziertz foxtrot teams
范哲思狐步舞队
payback on fanboy
对粉丝的回报
phoenix and bob
凤凰和鲍勃
on touch wingman
触摸翼人
roast
烘烤
do you bring building the alarm
你会不会带着警报器
rottenfield and nucleation understood songs answers
罗顿费尔德和成核的理解歌曲答案
the attain is the landlord to go to gucci guitar
诣是房东去古奇吉他
and agahani lula and machons and laga and shorsha
和阿加尼-卢拉和马孔斯和拉加和肖沙
i held the english ago frustectician decent biden bauer
我在英国举行的会议上说："我是一个很有礼貌的拜登-鲍尔。
ela anglos quarter eschevadovat
which morton lufka kitten on yaga defent from ganadatsur
哪一个Morton Lufka kitten on Yaga defent from ganadatsur
survived yef archtensch varne de granseuma cliet
拯救了一个又一个的 "大人物"。
bashisti uos s lady gulf paralleum in tomahawkar
Bashisti uos s lady gulf paralleum in tomahawkar
kitten defiantly hebazes here
小猫咪在这里很有可能会被人欺负。
that was what their own friends are stood
这就是他们自己的朋友所站的位置
the old site piston c is its finding oakman on dricy cicon
旧址活塞C是其在Dricy Cicon上找到Oakman的。
latin delanga
拉丁美洲的DELANGA
and its obsique von flucton
和它的obsique von flucton
in front of tomahawk's evangel for fate hall
在托默霍克的命运大厅前的福音
defers into oscibonifol
递延到奥西博尼福尔
那很快要的嘛
sir
先生
be a raiden
做个莱登人
and it's alexit
它是Alexit
hey bradley bradley hey
嘿，布拉德利，布拉德利，嘿
to kansas
到堪萨斯州
maverick
特立独行
hey esther too
嗨，艾瑟也是
the oblique effect management
斜线效应管理
so cocation on my
因此，在我身上的定位
duncan
DUNCAN
fight sixty feet as your handle duncan
斗转星移
i'm in the air to captain
我在飞机上给机长打电话
dega 1 start claw and cuttleboard arts
德加1号启动爪子和卡纸艺术
dega reserve and the rashaft dega four start clas
德加保护区和拉沙夫特德加四期启动班级
dega three start clap
德加三号开始拍手
dega two start cla
德加二号启动爪
the light suits are gonna look and the top and stamp now
轻装上阵，现在就可以看了。
the right to stamp my god
踩踏我的神的权利
attacked
受到攻击的
they got two good started
他们有两个好的开始
they got three good started
他们有三个好的开始
they got foggers started
他们启动了雾化器
comanche dega one the ride for check it
科曼奇-德加的一个骑手检查它
comanche one one contact
科曼奇一对一联系
kinda find the detailer dega mission fartense copy
有点发现DEGA任务的副本。
dega signal tavada
德加信号塔瓦达
there goes yet spontavada boomshead of itubit
这就是伊图里的Spontavada Boomshead。
to the india fine gibbit for osuvalantes esicon
为Osuvalantes esicon向India fine gibbit捐款
comanche de gawan chatatos comanche
科曼奇-德-加万-查塔托斯-科曼奇
scatos qui dear commando roger
亲爱的罗杰突击队员
they got on good
他们相处得很好
tomahawk skished outfit
战斧式的装备
yet skeets kitesoik
然而skeets kitesoik
there goes i'm graceful mato
我是优雅的马图
the gas behind tila fluke swimming noon on the isisicon and dry
蒂拉-弗鲁克背后的气体游泳中午在isisicon和干
small pines mark two mark three mark four mark
小松树 分值二 分值三 分值四 分值
yesterday kitten bars
昨天的小猫酒吧
are sea
是海
bones
骨骼
swive you not miss some tear
请你不要错过一些眼泪
copy zit and pasi curtains like a rooster cotto
抄袭痘痘和pasi窗帘像公鸡一样的cotto
degar comanche
德加-科曼奇
fine fruit target deloved iron of weapons by contactor
精细的水果靶子和武器的铁器。
quglum de blitzler here launched legend patholia
quglum de blitzler在这里推出了传奇的路径。
comanche vias de pauls from my fans park no
我的粉丝公园里的科曼奇-维阿斯-德-保罗斯没有
no no fenta equals at best zantanzi fernanza see this mistafe
不，不，芬达最多等于赞坦齐-费尔南扎看到这个误解。
he isn't in des econa de tomahawks
他不在DES ECONA de Tomahawks中
angeland antibiom the suits of her tiding
安吉拉的抗生素在她的衣服上。
the mission foreign d'azan deshini katahun
国外D'azan Deshini Katahun的任务
the grand glandman fathers in his office
大格兰德曼的父亲在他的办公室里
sir there gets two and four in hintadim type plan types
先生，在hintadim类型的计划类型中，有两个和四个。
until enemy notes fantash
直到敌人注意到Fantash
tomahawk and shlak and dry svo
战斧和Shlak和干Svo
thanks luck finally his whole fancy
谢谢你的运气，最后他的整个花式
skirt
裙子
bandits and a cross of atadigonga sears bruce obisco
匪徒和阿塔迪贡加-西尔斯-布鲁斯-奥比斯克的十字架
blows rooster bendits come near give us inside put mandipster
吹响了公鸡的号角，靠近了给我们里面放Mandipster。
what was my trainers
我的培训师是什么
sir lennons
伦纳德先生
it's five minute perform tier degas and minotifum tier
这是5分钟的表演层级的Degas和MINOTIFUM层级
marshan rooster dig manzanzu
马山公鸡挖曼珠沙华
lloyd of a pint of enclavis ethnelavian
劳埃德的一品脱英吉利酒业公司
then beneath often then defended santiatronophons
然后经常在下面，然后防守的santiatronophons
sacrifice tons of that
牺牲掉的那些
i come no one to answer this thing to santa
我没有人回答这个问题给圣诞老人
i'm the bruce dan extortioner goods clever goods
我是布鲁斯-丹敲诈勒索的货物，聪明的货物
whoa roosters after
哇，公鸡后
sir they got too hot with that off
先生，他们把它关掉后变得太热了
good
很好
my sister couldn't subtit
我妹妹不会做字幕
bob laser chet
鲍勃-激光切特
north bolton check up controls laser cultivated
北博尔顿检查控制激光培养的
and sex at a laser moonlight
和激光月光下的性爱
i'm planted
我被种下了
i need to slice a shit hey man listen
我需要切开一个狗屎，嘿，伙计，听着
to the electricity
呼叫电
see you mackie at bob
再见，麦基在鲍勃
they got three
他们得到了三个
step five head mash up up come stand by
第五步 头部碾压上来，准备就绪
they can't see their past see their past bump moss
他们看不到自己的过去，看到自己的过去凸起的苔藓
ah
啊
telephone face taking a punch headphone he finds headphone
电话脸挨了一拳，他找到了耳机
that's love unknown in my eyes
在我眼里，这就是未知的爱
they got two starters
他们有两个首发球员
that's my fault it's my laser no bruce not in the stimulum laser
这是我的错，这是我的激光器，没有布鲁斯，没有刺激性的激光器。
laser shiza
镭射石扎
please hope john please hope john i'm not an intention
请希望约翰，请希望约翰，我不是故意的。
confirm myself
确认我自己
you
你
know
知道
采访采访采访
yeah
是的
von dunham at spy they told a solar contest
冯-德纳姆在 "他们告诉我一个太阳 "比赛中的表现
no put me a snitch yourself
不把我当成一个告密者自己
let's
让我们
get
得到
those
那些
rooster status
公鸡状态
thank god
感谢上帝
i keep the monsters
我保留了那些怪物
contact negative
联系 负面
they got one outfit
他们有一件衣服
need to meet me about how do i treat it
需要满足我关于如何处理它的问题
how do i man no one
我怎么会没有人
who set up fire than you
谁设置了火比你
they got to outfit
他们得到了装备
baby
婴幼儿
shots are cutting touchscope on the air booster outside outside
镜头对准空气增压机上的切口，外面的镜头。
east and easy
东易日盛
dagger one guitarten if you don't want a dagger one guitar shots
如果你不想要一个匕首一吉他镜头，那么匕首一吉他就会出现在这里。
dagger one startles
匕首一惊
startles city
惊愕的城市
imat city
伊玛特市
imat there go one common the yakai fashum gazin nima snowmdrig
我有一个常见的雅凯法苏姆凝视尼玛的雪橇。
commandshi medita manfluke
命令希-梅迪塔-曼弗卢克
tia farmato and firebarite and four in a daga corsuit
Tia Farmato和Firebarite以及四位在Daga corsuit的人
i am in utabism contact
我在乌托邦的联系
horns is it too exophat
犄角旮旯是不是也是外来的？
aladegas to rictor bars are spending the
从阿拉德加斯到里克托尔的酒吧都是花钱买的。
backhand horse this is the beverage songs
后手马这是饮料歌曲
ema cunniest from everett told nith and an affidantness arte
来自埃弗里特的Ema Cunniest告诉记者，他是一个有亲和力的艺术家。
degas pear abidashat alabnester love comes is your own
德加斯梨阿比达沙特阿拉布内斯特爱来是你自己的事
negativ spare
消极备用
that don't suck sean staff negatif niece meet benderton dela
这并不吸人眼球的Sean工作人员Negatif侄女满足Benderton dela
about sir
关于先生
maverigo stopping even though the nichnokima nflion
虽说尼诺克玛Nflion停止了工作
wolfens is a truck
狼人是一辆卡车
daga nisht and kratham espitahola nasht and kratham
Daga nisht and kratham espitahola nasht and kratham
they got tootsa rutsabazas peshtating
他们得到了tootsa rutsabazas peshtating。
peshtating rosta de bendits come near beconishunkya
rosta
巡回演出
yes taught
是的教
maverick is taught
特立独行的人被教导
they got two escatoffen
他们得到了两个ESCATOFFEN
they got two common
他们有两个共同点
they got two heavens in this
他们在这里有两个天堂
they got two common
他们有两个共同点
arisca yeah ariscar i'll bet you
arisca 是的，ariscar 我和你打赌。
that's a must fans to you
这是你的必修课
that's a human thanks to each happy raquitov
这是对每个快乐的拉基托夫人的感谢
which collect the b to yawn by milan
哪些人收集了米兰的B打哈欠
is to shut the slaves of tim tarangazo a captiera slim garage
是关上蒂姆-塔兰加索的奴隶，是关上卡普蒂拉的苗条车库
haptira slim garated newer dark of kamesan
哈普提拉细长的嘎拉达的较新的卡梅山的黑暗
that's how studio blows stop i get out
工作室就是这样被吹停的，我出来了
who has megazachtizolistic
谁拥有Megazachtizolistic
now here
现在在这里
shanditas in
Шартаниения
it's our shanditas in
这是我们的山迪达斯在
and thus money it
并因此获得金钱
this is nichten hanst
这是不可能的。
this mr thar
这位先生
and i have felt sin in zoana
我在Zoana感受到了罪恶
we try mixed up crucials
我们尝试混合的十字路口
we have a snish map to kiss and afflict
我们有一张可以亲吻和折磨人的Snish地图
fit vizards map
合适的维扎兹地图
okay
好的
that father's in logic bath yep
那位父亲在逻辑上是在洗澡 是的
that rips end of me okay
撕开我的底线好吗
good idea yeah that's good
好主意 是的，这很好
then have anything that's seizing you okay
那么，有什么东西在抓住你吗？
charges here i am miss the answer of iron spansey state
我在这里错过了铁道部的答案。
and the slippers started
和拖鞋开始
tends to defend them or do tsana and nanseka her son yeah
倾向于为他们辩护，或者做沙娜和Nanseka她的儿子是的。
surprise
惊喜
okay
好的
is the valet of my smack
是我的打火机的男仆
oh my god it's dusting odd
哦，我的上帝，它的尘土飞扬的怪事
all of it
所有的
by the pistons and touched earth
被活塞触及的大地
the king that is a museum sir
馆长的国王
a company titlation now is matt
现在的公司名称是Matt
may have to assist an ecology i'm a stun
可能要协助一个生态学，我是个愣头青
but i'll said you miss a sincere quarter politic math goldfister
但我说你错过了一个真诚的季度政治数学金菲斯特
come come back lasha better get off come
来吧，回来吧，Lasha最好下车来。
go so come come come
去吧，来吧，来吧
sir the amphanganzigan iphone rustas north parazanda
先生 amphanganzigan iphone rustas north parazanda
shined aban and fairfank tsunsohavan
Shined Aban和Fairfank tsunsohavan
it's kinda autong merkley doctor aba
这是一个有点自相矛盾的Merkley医生ABA
epivitimatibashai
ǞǞǞǞ
it is very neroft
很软
for meeting sir
见先生
lufthamiba bahung
melod and feltz and tom kat mccourse of unza reposition
Melod和Feltz以及UNZA的Tom Kat Mccourse重新定位
on mercy
关于怜悯
maverick
特立独行
okay rooster they've been known sweetham trey ajaba tadan
好吧，公鸡，他们已经被称为Sweetham Trey Ajaba Tadan
fonkas todd canada
冯卡斯-托德-加拿大
your hitness alice todd
尊敬的艾利斯-陶德先生
that's mozzashma zagan ok yes that's funka and then does
那是Mozzashma Zagan 好的，那是Funka，然后呢？
that's where if thwar's what is ishhangdafiya first dammit
这是在哪里，如果战争的是什么ishhangdafiya第一dammit
your hit and get sky hundreds as you're home gets
在你回家的时候，你被击中并得到天空中的几百块钱。
miss yangunawa kinda i know
我知道
by the uptail in front of them dead
在他们面前的上尾巴死了
there's clicks on ross
罗斯身上有点击率
yeah
是的
friend four teeth ty five foot dog
朋友四齿蒂五脚狗
that's malcolm bayette
那是马尔科姆-巴耶特
okay her too bloodbine far cool
好吧，她也是血脉相通的人。
and you bust me a via zinfango sean tort
你通过津帆戈-西恩-托特给我打了电话
ok see come
好的，再见
peace that plan
和平计划
is that cinemasco
那是电影院吗？
at the same time visit exam tvd
同时访问考试TVD
cerron vicoma glacia
沧海一粟
bancoma glacia
苁蓉
that's a suspensation what's up there kinda how long
这是个悬念，上面有什么东西，有多长？
i know how long i said
我知道我说了多长时间
and that's it ignidi na inhabishovna niggazi
就这样，Ignidi na inhabishovna niggazi
shit
大便
sir and whitman get a trust position
先生和怀特曼获得信任职位
good hutsu
好的Hutsu
benny sagatsi's threatening to often you but i am cough
Benny Sagatsi威胁要经常找你，但我在咳嗽。
that's as such loud as it's
这就像它的声音一样响亮
math convert into commission
数学转换为佣金
cutter
切割机
that that's not comfort
这不是安慰
i know it fills in giving yegadif and finger nazijon
我知道它填补了给Yegadif和手指Nazijon的空白。
as the sneakers floatside as the step he lord
作为运动鞋浮动的步骤，他主
the nation nature be reversed with mahon
马宏的国家性质被颠覆了
that would have best you
这将是你最好的选择
comes from math
来自于数学
nish denton
tossa and fuck
抛出和操
i can't i can't
我不能 我不能
你们为什么不吃饭
拿下面向下书
boom boom boom
轰轰轰轰轰轰
yes sir
是的，先生
he was deep back in the sahari in the titani tina fraser
他在撒哈拉沙漠的深处，在蒂塔尼-弗雷泽的车里。
he sees abs to a staff born a ship
他看到了腹肌，以一个工作人员出生的船
no hell no gun
没有地狱没有枪
does that get tough turn down
那会不会很难受呢？
tina best issues
婷婷的最佳问题
cannot accuse me
不能指责我
consummate
圆满
i needed sessions to shut them
我需要会议来关闭他们
comes from memory
源于记忆
你呀
mafia shut the swunk of the car on yours
黑手党把你的车的车头关上
i've been once rid of tiger that's her ladies
我曾经摆脱过老虎，那是她的女人。
oh my god
哦，我的上帝
that that foister can
该泡沫可以
france on us
法国对我们
i dumped kenny williams
我甩了肯尼-威廉姆斯
like keita rooster touch camp
像凯塔公鸡触摸营
that's fucking up
那是他妈的
can a touch camp on my map
能否在我的地图上触摸营地
i said
我说
this is good
这很好
oh luckah hate melissa george
讨厌梅丽莎-乔治
the academy next absolutely you
旁边的学院绝对是你
miss an alstein plus
怀念阿尔斯坦加
the volca mirror losing silence as arsemany saga
沃尔卡镜像失去了沉默，因为阿瑟曼尼的传奇故事
nine merton whose escape distant master
九个默顿，他逃出了远方的主人
yes she's a thousand who's the tiny shout out sneakers get late
是的，她是一千人，谁的小喊声运动鞋得到晚了
he stood be light
他站着就是光
he stood be light cause
他站着的时候是轻的，因为
rocal attack ladies on gentlemen yes based euretta
蓄意攻击女士们和先生们 是的，以尤里塔为基地
little engzi de zishad squadra and cluttons eulatashana fawn
小Engzi de Zishad squadra和Cluttons eulatashana小鹿
on martin zizis behind salando
关于萨兰多背后的马丁-齐兹斯
hey hangman says good oz hey he ben good rosta
刽子手说："好的盎司，他是好的罗斯塔"。
he's been so good
他一直都很好
beverage of gignant fluke can fanfadak can fang
饮品中的 "侥幸 "可以是 "范法达 "也可以是 "方"。
hart zylan fernon fangnachban dekoyman dekoyman fannachbang los
HART ZYLAN FERNON FANGNACHBAN DEKOYMAN DEKOYMAN FANNACHBANG LOS
let the zach reds make sure how to take that club
让扎克-红军确保如何拿下该俱乐部
let's go into the socks sentence okay
让我们进入袜子的句子，好吗？
it's a good investance
这是一个很好的投资项目
nothing else is for death but just fire
死无对证，只许州官放火
merford finn and it is ear as us
Merford Finn和它是我们的耳朵
cat metro cat metro
猫咪地铁 猫咪地铁
thank you to submit us leaving you at the test
谢谢你提交给我们，让我们在测试中离开你。
and demand dead architect
和要求死亡的建筑师
hey matt
嘿，马特
jimmy
姜文
is the
是指
is penida
是penida
the isthmid emilia oftenham ziegler turn
伊思密特-艾米利亚-常哈姆-齐格勒的转身
had to get zach fancy vi that's alexand
不得不让扎克看上了⑥，这是亚历山大。
nine had finished
九人已完成